forexwealthcatalysts.com 2015-12-25

# Profits Run - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to Profits Run, Inc. (referred to herein as “ **our company** ”, “ **we** ” or “ **us** ”). We want to make your experience on our website as enjoyable and profitable as possible and want you to use, with complete confidence, the Services and Products (as defined below) that we offer.

We have created this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) to demonstrate our commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects, uses and maintains information from the people (a) who use our Internet services (“ **Services** ”), (b) who visit our website and may access some of our Services without having an account with us (“ **Visitors** ”) and (c) who purchase products (“ **Products** ”) and pay a fee to subscribe to our Services (“ **Members** ”). This Privacy Policy sets out the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection, use and maintenance of this information. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Introduction: Our company collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our websites or use our Products or Services. We use this information mainly to provide a personalized experience as you use our Products and Services. Our company generally does not share this information with third parties, except as provided for herein.

Upon Registration: Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when signing up for our Products and Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information, (such as credit card number) and the type of personal computer being used to access Services. Personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member’s account (e.g., for billing purposes.) This personal information is not shared with third parties, except as provided for herein. We may also generate general non-identifying profile information from the personal information that Members provide during registration (e.g., total number of Members, but not Member names), and such information may be used to sell advertisements.

With Partners: Some Products and Services may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contract seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Members with some of these Products and Services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In such cases, your personal information may be shared as provided for herein.

Shopping: If you order Products or Services from our company, we will use the personal information you provide only to process the order. We do not share this information with outside parties, except to the extent necessary to complete the order.

Advertisements: Our company may display online advertisements. In those cases we share general non-identifying profile information about our Visitors and Members collected during the registration process, through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers. In some cases, we use this general non-identifying profile information to deliver specific advertisements and for joint ventures. For example, an advertiser or joint venture company specifies the audience that they desire to reach and they provide our company with an advertisement tailored to that particular audience. Based upon the general non-identifying profile information we have collected, we may then display or send the advertisement to the intended people. Our company does not share personal information of Visitors or Members with these advertisers or joint venture partners.

Responses to Email Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to our company, the inquiry is answered using the return email address. Our company does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with anyone else, except as provided for herein.

Voluntary Customer Surveys: We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide our company with important information which helps improve the types of Products and Services offered and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in customer surveys is voluntary.

We may combine the information that our company receives from people responding to our surveys and responses of other customers to prepare broader, general responses to the survey questions (e.g., age, gender, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry and other demographic information). Our company may then use this information to improve the quality of the Products and Services provided to you and to develop new Products and Services. This general non-identifying profile information may be shared with third parties.

Sharing Information: It is our company’s policy not to use or share the personal information we collect about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to the methods described in this Privacy Policy without also providing you the opportunity to opt out and prohibit such unrelated disclosures. The following are permissible uses of sharing of personal information about Visitors or Members by our company, unless you elect to opt-out:

From time to time, we will share your postal address with other companies that offer products, services, or information that you might enjoy for purposes of sending you a special offer via direct mail. To opt-out of this direct-mail sharing offer, you can have your name put on our “do not share” list by writing to us at Profits Run Inc, 28339 Beck Rd., Unit F1, Wixom, MI 48393 or sending an email to support@profitsrun.com.

When our company and a partner jointly promote our Products or Services, we may provide the partner some personal information such as the name, address and user name of the persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion solely for the purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this case, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose.

Also, we may disclose information about Visitors, Members or information concerning your use of the Services or Products or websites accessible through the use of our Services or Products for any reason to credit agencies, collection agencies and law enforcement, if we (in our sole discretion) determine that it is reasonable to do so (as permitted by applicable law, if any) or as required by law.

In addition, our company may disclose personal information we collect, if our company received your prior permission to do so has been received.

Our Anti-Spam Policy:

Our Company has a no tolerance spam policy and we comply with all anti-spam laws. Every promotional email we send contains a mandatory unsubscribe link which you can use to be removed from our mailing list. Further, any third party affiliate, partner, or other entity are prohibited from promoting our products and services with unsolicited email (spam).

If you believe we have sent you unsolicited email, please send an email to support@profitsrun.com, or call us at 248-344-4440.

“Cookies”: A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. Our company may use “cookies” to collect, store and track data for statistical purposes to improve the Products and Services we provide and to manage our networks.

If you are a Visitor or Member, we may use cookies to save your settings and provide customized and personal service. These cookies do not allow any third parties to access any of your customer information. Advertisers and partners may also use cookies. We have no control over their actions, and we specifically disclaim any responsibility for their actions.

“Advertising”: We partner with third party ad networks to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. We use remarketing and display advertising across multiple networks including, but not limited to, Google. Our ad network partners and other third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests on sites across the internet. We may target ads based on data provided by clients or partners in combination with the data we collect ourselves. The data provided by third parties may originate both online and offline. We may share the aggregate information we collect with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. Our advertising partners including but not limited to Google, also place persistent cookies on your device when you visit our website or our Advertisers’ websites in order to help us recognize you and serve relevant advertisements to you when you visit their website or online service or websites in their networks.

Children Privacy Laws: The privacy of children is important to all of us. To ensure compliance with any applicable children privacy laws, we restrict our website to people 18 years of age or over.

You must be 18 years of age or over to access this website. If you are under 18 years of age, you are not permitted to access this website for any reason. We do not monitor our website for compliance with any applicable children privacy laws.

Our Company’s Commitment to Data Security: The Services and websites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of data under our control. While we take all reasonably necessary steps to protect the integrity and security of our data and networks, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent “third party” hackers or systems from illegally accessing our data.

We will revise or update this policy if our practices change, or as we develop better ways to keep you informed about them. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. If we decide to change this policy, we will post a new policy on our site and change the date at the bottom. Changes to the policy shall not apply retroactively.

Updated: May 5, 2015
